Copelof, Maxwell Arbitration Briefs, Exhibits, Transcripts and Decisions 5129
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Thirty Regular Stitch Edge Operators., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  2/26/43. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Committee of Workers representing 531 Employees of the Scout Factory, Johnson City, NY., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  6/5/43. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Eleven "Goodyear Stitchers"., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  1/10/45. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Esmond Mills, Inc. vs. TWUA, Locals 392 and 486., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  4/8/48. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Evangeline Shoe Mfg. Co. vs. Committee Representing Ten Cutters., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  12/21/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Everlastik, Inc. vs. TWUA, Local 382., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Fales, L.F. Co. vs. USW, Local 3722., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  Issue: discipline - discharge. no decision.
- Faulkner & Colony Mfg. Co. vs. UTWA, Local 2346., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  6/6/46. Issue: rates of pay.
- Faulkner & Colony Mfg. Co. vs. UTWA, Local 2346., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  11/20/46. Issue: rates of pay.
- Fisher-Price Toys, Inc. vs. Playthings, Jewelry & Novelty Workers International Union, Local 503., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  8/4/44. Issue: contract modification.
- Fitchburg Yarn Co. vs. TWUA, Local 278., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  7/15/49. Issue: arbitrability; assignment of jobs - change of duties.
- Fitchburg Yarn Co. vs. TWUA, Local 278., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  3/3/45. Issue: vacancies - seniority.
- Fitzgibbons, E.P. & Son vs. BSAC, Cut Sale Local., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  9/24/42. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Fleetwood Airflow, Inc. vs. USW, Sub-district #9, Local 3573., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  4/29/49. Issue: supervisors & foremen - bargaining unit work - performance of - layoff; working conditions - protective clothing; sick leave & sick pay; lay off - seniority; assignment of jobs - seniority; layoff - transfers.
- Fleisher Shoe Co. vs. Rosario Lassette, et. al., employees of Sale Laying Dept., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Fleisher Shoe Co. vs. Fourteen Lasters., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  9/27/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Forman & Gumner Co. vs. ILGWU, Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt & Dressmakers Union., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  5/22/46. Issue: rates of pay.
- Frank & Seder, of Pittsburgh, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks' Int'l. Protective Assoc., Local 1365., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  6/20/41. Issue: rates of pay.
- French Worsted Co. vs. Industrial Trades Union of America., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  3/30/45. Issue: standards of production - workload; rates of pay - differentials in pay.
- Geisenheimer-Lewin Inc. vs. Underwear & Negligee Workers Union, Local 62., 1938 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  12/10/38. Issue: rates of pay - discrimination. no decision.
- General Bronze Corp. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  12/13/43. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- General Cable Corp. vs. Int'l. Bro. of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local B-1164., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  6/7/46. Issue: transfers - seniority.
- General Seafood Corp. vs. Atlantic Fishermen's Union., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  no decision.
- General Cable Corp. vs. Int'l. Bro. of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local B-1164., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  7/3/43. Issue: vacations; rates of pay - equal pay for equal work.
- Gerstein & Cooper Co. vs. USW, Local 3128., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  2/12/47. Issue: management rights - job content.
- Gimbel Bros. vs. Retail Clerks Int'l. Protective Assoc., Local 1365., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  6/16/41. Issue: contract modification - rates of pay.
- Gimbel Bros. vs. Stenographers, Bookkeepers, Typists, Accountants & Assistants Union of Pittsburg., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  10/13/41. Issue: contract modification - rates of pay
- Gimbels Thirty-Third St. & Saks Thirty-Fourth St. vs. Dept. Store Employees Union, Local 2., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  11/30/49. Issue: reinstatement.
- Gimbel Bros. vs. General Warehousemen & Employees Union, Local 636., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Givren Shoe Co., E.J. vs. BSAC., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  9/17/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Gold Seal Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 1., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  1/22/44. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Gold Seal Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 1., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  8/12/42. Issue: discipline - discharge; strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages.
- Gold Seal Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 1., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  9/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Gold Seal Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 1., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  9/11/42. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Gold Seal Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 1., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  9/15/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Gold Seal Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 1., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  1/27/43. Issue: bargaining units - employees within bargaining unit.
- Gold Seal Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 1., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  8/25/43. Issue: assignment of jobs.
- Goldberg Bros. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council #20., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  10/5/44. Issue: rates of pay.
- Goldman & Ostrow vs. United Wholesale & Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  8/25/41. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Goldman & Ostrow vs. United Wholesale & Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  3/2/42. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Goodall-Sanford, Inc. vs. UTWA, Local 1802., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  4/10/45. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Goodall-Sanford, Inc. vs. UTWA, Local 1802., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  4/18/45. Issue: reinstatement.
- Goodall-Sanford, Inc. vs. UTWA, Local 1802., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  6/22/45. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Goodall-Sanford, Inc. vs. UTWA, Local 1802., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  8/1/45. Issue: rates of pay - standards of production
- Gorton Pew Fisheries Co., Ltd. vs. Int'l. Longshoremen's Association (ILA), Gloucester Seafood Workers Union, Series 1572-1., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  9/28/48. Issue: transfers - temporary.
- Graceform-Camlin Corset Co., vs. ILGWU, Cutters Local 10., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  4/8/41. Issue: assignment of jobs - qualifications.
- Great American Plastic Co. vs. United Novelty Celluloid Workers, Local 61., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  12/24/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Greater Boston Hebrew Master Bakers, Inc. vs. Bakery & Confectionery Workers Int'l. Union of America, Local 45., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  2/24/45. Issue: overtime - rates of pay.
- Greyhound Terminal of Columbus, Inc. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 1042., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  5/9/49. Issue: reinstatement.
- Hamilton Schen & Walsh Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 59., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  11/30/45. Issue: rates of pay.
- Harjer Furniture Ltd. vs. UFW, Local 76-B., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  12/27/47. Issue: insurance - employer contributions.
- Harodite Finishing Co., Inc. vs. TWUA, Local 469., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  11/26/43. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority.
- Harold Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council #20., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  2/12/44. Issue: rates of pay.
- Harrison Abrasive Corp. vs. Federal Local Metal Abrasive Workers, 22539., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  11/24/42. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Harrison Abrasive Corp. vs. Federal Labor Union 22539., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  6/48. Issue: promotions - seniority.
- Hartman Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Jt. Council #20., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Haverhill Shoe Manufacturers Board of Trade, Haverhill, MA vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Jt. Council #20., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  11/8/44. Issue: rates of pay.
- Hemphill Co. vs. Banner Protective Association., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  7/30/43. Issue: rates of pay; rates of pay - shift differentials; vacation pay; holidays & holiday pay; rates of pay - incentive pay; grievance and grievance procedure.
- Henderson Cotton Mills vs. TWUA, Local 584., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  10/4/47. Issue: rates of pay; classification of jobs.
- Hingham Water Co. vs. Int'l. Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), Local 849., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  6/7/45. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Holtz, Herbert Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council #20., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Holtz, Herbert Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council #20., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  12/31/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Holtz, Herbert Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council #20., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  6/1/44. Issue: rates of pay.
- Homer Commutator Corp. vs. UE, Local 735., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  3/23/42. Issue: contract modification.
- Hood Rubber Co., a division of B.F. Goodrich Co. vs. Federal Local Union 21914., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  11/3/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Horne, Joseph Co. vs. Stenographers, Bookkeepers, Typists, Accounts & Assistants' Union of Pittsburgh, PA, Local 20959., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  8/2/41. Issue: contract modification - wage adjustments.
- Horne, Joseph Co. vs. Retail Clerks Int'l. Protective Assoc., Local 1365., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Hubbard Shoe Co., Inc. vs. Eagle Shoe Workers, Inc., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  10/3/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Hubbard Shoe Co., Inc. vs. Eagle Shoe Workers, Inc., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  1/16/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Hubbard Shoe Co., Inc. vs. Eagle Shoe Workers, Inc., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  3/26/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Hubbard Shoe Co., Inc. vs. Eagle Shoe Workers, Inc., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  11/24/44. Issue: rates of pay.
- Hubbard Shoe Co., Inc. vs. Eagle Shoe Workers, Inc., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  6/25/45. Issue: rates of pay; discipline - discharge.
- Hubbard Shoe Co., Inc. vs. Eagle Shoe Workers, Inc., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  9/10/46. Issue: rates of pay.
- Hudson Pulp & Paper Corp. vs. UE, Local 218., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  4/29/48. Issue: contract modification - wage adjustment.
- Int'l. Shoe Company, Bryon Factory vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 140-A., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  5/28/43. Issue: rates of pay; rates of pay - increase.
- Int'l. Shoe Company, Higginsville, MO plant vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 137-A., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  12/16/48. Issue: rates of pay.
- International Shoe Company, Cohas Factory vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 148-A., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  11/21/44. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Int'l. Shoe Company, Nashua, NH vs.. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 128-A., 1945 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  3/12/45. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Int'l. Shoe Company, Cohas Factory vs.. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 147-A., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  6/1/43. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- International Shoe Company, Cohas Factory vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 147-A., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  5/18/44. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Ideal Electric & Mfg. Co. & UE, Local 758., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  5/21/48. Issue: layoff - seniority.
- Inland Waterways Corp. and Nat'l. Maritime Union of America., 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  12/12/45. Issue: discharge - intoxication.
- International Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America (USWA), Local 160-A., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  3/20/47. Issues: 1) rates of pay. 2) change in operations. 3) rate revisions, change in operation. 4) rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 128-A., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  5/20/44. Issues: rate revision - change in product.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 168-A., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  11/14/47. Issue: incentive pay - rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 168-A., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  11/17/48. Issue: a) reinstatement following physical disability. b) rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 185-A. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Issue: rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 100-A., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  8/30/47. Issue: a) reinstatement - leave of absence. b) layoff - as discipline - unsatisfactory work. c) rate revisions.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 100-A., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  2/20/48. Issue: rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 100-A., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  9/14/48. Issue: rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 107., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  6/21/48. Issues: rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 104-A., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  12/1/48. Issue: rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 104-A., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  1/2/48. Issues: 1) rate revision. 2) rate revision. 3) foreman - return to the bargaining unit.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 109-A., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  12/21/44. Issues: rate revision, retroactive pay.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  6/8/48. Issues: rate revision - change in operations.
- Int'l. Shoe Co. vs. USWA, Local 104-A., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  5/5/48. Issues: 1) rates of pay - combined jobs. 2) rate revision. 3) rate revision. 4) rates of pay - discrimination. 5) rate revision.
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Manchester, NH vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 109-A., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  6/1/43. Issue: rates of pay - inequities; rates of pay - increase.
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Manchester, NH vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 109-A., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  5/19/44. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Washington, MO vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 118-A., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  6/5/48. Issue: rates of pay.
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Sullivan, MO vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 120-A., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  2/28/48. Issue: rates of pay - piecework vs. day work; rates of pay.
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Sullivan, MO vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 120-A., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  11/48. Issue: layoff - discrimination; rates of pay - computation change
- Int'l. Shoe Co., Cape Giraudeau Factory vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 125-A., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  1/22/49. Issue: rates of pay -change of operations; transfers - promotions; vacancies - transfers
- Jagger Bros., Inc. vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers of America, Local 1802., 1942 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  2/7/42. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Joan Plush Mills vs. Industrial Trades Union., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  4/3/47. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Jones & Lamson Machine Co. vs. UE, Local 218., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  10/7/46. Issue: classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors
- Juilliard, A.D., Co. Inc. vs. TWUA., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  10/29/48. Issue: arbitrability; standards of pay - workload.
- Kane, Dunham & Kraus, Inc. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 110-A., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  12/19/45. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Kaufmann Dept. Stores, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks Protective Assoc., Local 1365., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  8/16/41. Issue: rates of pay.
- Kaufmann Dept. Stores, Inc. vs. Salesmen Furniture Dept., Local 101., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  10/13/41. Issue: rates of pay - commissions; vacation pay
- Kelly, George A. Co. vs. General Teamsters Union, Local 249., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  6/9/47. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Kent Shoe Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council No. 20., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  4/3/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Kent Shoe Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council No. 20., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  11/18/43. Issue: rates of pay
- Kent Shoe Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council No. 20., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  12/5/43. Issue: rates of pay -standards of production.
- Kent Shoe Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council No. 20., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Kent Shoe Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council No. 20., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  10/7/44. Issue: rates of pay.
- Kent Shoe Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council No. 20., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  2/10/45. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment
- Kent Shoe Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council No. 20., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  6/23/45. Issue: rates of pay.
- Ketcham, G.M. Mfg. Corp. vs. United Wire & Metal Workers Union, Local 36., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  4/22/47. Issue: arbitrability - rates of pay.
- Ketcham, G.M. Mfg. Corp. vs. United Wire & Metal Workers Union, Local 36., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  6/2/47. Issue: layoff - seniority; discipline - discharge; transfers - temporary; reinstatement.
- Keystone Bakery, Inc. vs. Bakery Drivers Union, Local 485., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  12/27/41. Issue: vacation pay.
- Kleber Trunk & Bag Co. vs. Int'l. Ladies Hand Bags, Pocket-books & Novelty Workers Union, Luggage Workers Union, Local 55., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  7/25/41. Issue: rates of pay
- Knapp Bros. Shoe Mfg. vs. BSAC, Lasters' Local., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  6/26/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Knapp Bros. Shoe Mfg. vs. BSAC, Dressers & Packers Local., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  3/15/44. Issue: rates of pay
- Knapp Bros. Shoe Mfg. vs. BSAC, Vampers Local., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  4/16/45. Issue: rates of pay
- Labor Standards Assoc. vs. United Department Store Employees, Local 101, and Retail Clerks Int'l. Protective Association, Local 1365., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  12/7/43. Issue: rates of pay - commissions.
- Lafayette Worsted Spinning Co. vs. Industrial Trades Union., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  10/26/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Laughlin, Thomas Co. vs. IAM, Lodge 1256., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  10/18/46. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Leominster Tool Co., Inc. vs. UE, Local 286., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  8/7/47. Issue: vacation pay
- Leona Mfg. Co. vs. UTWU, Local 116., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  12/31/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Levy, Harris vs. United Wholesale & Warehouse Employees Union, Local 65., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  11/27/41. Issue: union representatives & business - time off for union business.
- Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Co. vs. Federation of Glass, Ceramic & Silica Sand Workers of America., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  7/29/46. Issue: rates of pay - incentive pay.
- Limerick Yarn Mills vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers of America, Local 2643., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  2/10/44. Issue: seniority
- Linde Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council 20., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  8/21/44. Issue: rates of pay
- Lindstrom Corp. vs. Playthings, Jewelry & Novelty Workers Int'l. Union, Local 433., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  2/21/48. Issue: rates of pay.
- Lisson-Melen Co. vs. UFW, Local 132., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  11/26/41. Issue: rates of pay - increase; vacation pay
- Lisson-Melen Co. vs. UFW, Local 132., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  5/25/46. Issue: seniority-layoff; rates of pay; vacation pay - eligibility
- Lisson-Melen Co. vs. UFW, Local 132., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  10/5/49. Issue: rates of pay.
- Lister Worsted Co. vs. UTWA, Local 35., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  6/11/46. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Little Falls Felt Shoe Co., Inc. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 159., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  10/9/46. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Louis Heel Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, United Heel Workers of America., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  6/9/44. Issue: Interest arbitration. no decision.
- Lowenbraun, Harry vs. Fish Workers Union, Local 635., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  1/16/41. Issue: reduction in force.
- Lukens Steel Co. vs. Steel Workers Organizing Committee, Local 1165., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  8/15/41. Issue: classification of jobs; rates of pay.
- M.K.M. Hosiery Mills, Inc. vs. American Federation of Hosiery Workers, Branch 163., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  8/2/48. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Macy, R.H. & Co., Inc. vs. United Retail, Wholesale & Department Store Employees Union, Local 1-S., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  5/6/47. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Mades, M.M. Co. vs. United Packinghouse Workers of America, Local 11., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  10/14/49. Issue: discipline - discharge. no decision.
- Mades, M.M. Co. vs. United Packinghouse Workers of America, Local 11., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  11/20/48. Issue: layoff - seniority; vacancies - method of filling.
- Maguire Industries, Inc. vs. UE, Local 225., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  5/3/46. Issue: vacations - eligibility.
- Maiden Form Brassiere Co., Inc. vs. ILGWU, Local 160, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  9/16/40. Issue: layoff - layoff as discipline
- Marks, L.V. & Sons Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Marks Local 156., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  6/19/44. Issue: rates of pay; classification of jobs; rates of pay - adjustment; vacation pay.
- May Knitting Co. vs. United Wholesale & Warehouse Employees of New York, Local 65., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  8/22/41. Issue: hiring - management rights; union security - union shop; union representatives & business - admission to plant.
- Maybury Shoe Co. vs. Square Deal Organization, Inc., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  9/21/48. Issue: rates of pay.
- Mayflower Colonial Shops, Inc. vs. UFW, Local 136-B., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  5/16/44. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay; vacation pay; holidays & holiday pay.
- McLain Fire Brick Co. vs. United Brick & Clay Workers of America, Local 539 & 767., 1942 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  3/3/42. Issue: union security; vacations; rates of pay - increase; contracts - expiration date
- Merrimac Mills vs. Fed. of Woolen & Worsted Workers of America, Local 14., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  4/29/43. Issue: rates of pay - premium pay.
- Merrimac Mills vs. Fed. of Woolen & Worsted Workers of America, Local 14., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  1/7/44. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Metropolitan New York & New Jersey Casket Manufacturers Association., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  2/48. no decision.
- Milford Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 43., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  6/30/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Milford Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 43., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  1/1/44. Issue: rates of pay.
- Monarch Shoe Co., Inc. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 1., 1942 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  8/12/42. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Monomac Spinning Co. vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers., 1945 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  7/16/45. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Monsanto Chemical Co. vs. UE, Local 288., 1945 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  7/30/45. Issue: vacation pay; classification of jobs; working conditions - wash up time.
- Monsanto Chemical Co. vs. UE, Local 288., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  1/2/46. Issue: layoff - vacation pay; rates of pay - equal pay for equal work.
- Monsanto Chemical Co. vs. UE, Local 288., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  11/22/47. Issue: discipline - layoff.
- Monsanto Chemical Co. vs. UE, Local 288., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  1/7/49. Issue: assignment of jobs; insubordination - discipline
- Morgan, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 82., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  9/20/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Morrison Mills, Inc. vs. Federal Labor Union, Local 22824., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  7/17/46. Issue: rates of pay
- Murray Co. vs. UE, Local 272., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  4/23/43. Issue: union security - job jurisdiction; discipline - discharge.
- Murray Co. vs. UE, Local 272., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  10/2/44. Issue: discipline - suspension.
- Mutual Shoe Co. vs. Marlboro Shoe Workers Associates, Inc., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  10/30/43. Issue: reinstatement - following military service.
- National Casket Co., Inc. vs. Upholsterers' Int'l. Union, Local 560, 1928, and 412. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  no date. Issue: contract modification. no decision.